

Curriculum Vitae

Personal information

Name: Mr. José Luis Rasmussen Garcia

Telephone: +31 (0)641640176
Date of birth: 19 Sept 1983
Birthplace: Lima-Peru
Nationality: Dutch

E-mail: <u>j.l.rasmussengarcia@gmail.com</u>

Website: https://cv-joserasmussen.herokuapp.com/

LinkedIn: http://www.linkedin.com/in/josé-luis-rasmussen-garcia

GitHub: https://github.com/BabyLizzy-FunTime-Lab



My Objectives

My main goals as a web developer are to be client oriented and to never stop learning. Through my experience in healthcare and PostNL I learned that good communication between technicians, workers, management and clients is key to the success of most if not all projects. Although my focus right now is on sharpening my coding skills and creating, I would like to one day help bridge the gap between developers and clients.

Education

2004

Laacation	
2019 - present	HBO Full-Stack Web Developer Course (Ongoing), Leidse Onderwijsinstelling (LOI).
	This is a part-time Full-Stack Web development course. I have earned my HTML5 & CSS3 certificate and I am a certified CIW JavaScript Specialist. My next objective
l	is to finish the PHP/SQL module and the SCRUM module.
2017 - 2018	Web Development Intensive Course (Coding-Bootcamp Certificate), The New
l .	York Code & Design Academy (NYCDA), Amsterdam.
l .	I trained for 9 months at the NYCDA to become a junior full stack web developer.
l .	It was great to work in such a diverse multicultural group. The course covered
l	many subjects at highspeed. I got to work with, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery,
l .	React.js, Bootstrap, PUG, Node.js, Express.js, PostgreSQL and GitHub.
2011 - 2018	Healthcare Technology (First Year Diploma), Rotterdam University of Applied
l .	Sciences (Hogeschool Rotterdam).
l	This is where my love for coding started, by working on Arduinos and SQL. The
	most important things I learned here were, (table top) research, analyzing
l	complex problems in multidisciplinary research groups and my love for creating
l .	applications.
2006 - 2010	Physiotherapy (First Year Diploma) , University of Rotterdam University of Applied
	Sciences (Hogeschool Rotterdam).
l	During this time, I learned, among other things, self-reflection, critical thinking

tech so I switched to Healthcare Technology.

Pre-university secondary education.

VWO (Diploma), Colegio Arubano, Oranjestad – Aruba.







and clinical reasoning. However, early in 2010 I decided to pursue a career in



Languages

Spanish: Native language
English: Native language level
Dutch: Second language

Papiamento: Fluent

Work experience and Internships

2019 - 2021 PostNL (Part-Time Parcel Delivery), Depot Ridderkerk, Rotterdam This job taught me a lot about life and about people in general. Working outside makes you feel like you are part of life and not just an observer. 2018 **Internship: Analysis of medical alarms**, Bravis Hospital, Bergen op Zoom. I was given the task to investigate alarm fatigue on the children's and neonatal ward. I did enquiries, approached the personnel and tech companies and also analyzed CSV-2017 - 2018 Social media Consultant (remote part-time) and Stockroom assistant, Quality Auto Parts N.V. Aruba. I helped in the stockroom and modernized the way clients are reached (Facebook, WhatsApp & Google maps). I reported Google business results directly to management and provided customer support via Facebook chats. After the summer I worked parttime remotely from Rotterdam for about a year. 2016 Safe use of medical technology (internship), Diakonessenhuis hospital, Utrecht. It was my task to find a suitable e-learning course to educate hospital personnel on the safe use of medical technology. My project was part of a much bigger hospital wide safety project. 2012 - 2015 Assistant Landlord (part-time), Stadswonen Rotterdam. I was entrusted with receiving and handing out keys and dealt with tenant complaints. I also dealt with new tenants and reported issues to Stadswonen. Innovation in rehabilitation (minor project), Laurens Antonius Binnenweg 2013 - 2014 rehabilitation center, Rotterdam. In a multidisciplinary group we studied the effect of videogame therapies for stroke patients. As a result, we developed a physical interface prototype. It was published in the Laurens Magazine. 2013 - 2014 **Design for one (minor project+)**, *Erasmus MC, Rotterdam.* I had a consultant roll within another minor project group. I assisted in the creation of a workshop tool design for a client with an amputated arm. 2012 - 2013 Oxycodone delivery system (internship), Bravis hospital, Roosendaal.

Additional Information

Driver's License (AM-BE)

I have a Dutch driver's license and over 15 years of driving experience.

concept in an advisory report.

Playing guitar and gaming

I'm a student of the acoustic and the electric guitar. I hope to one day join or start a cover band. Playing videogames and Magic the Gathering are old hobbies of mine.

I researched the possibility of introducing a system that delivers on demand opioid pain medication pills (oxycodone). The system needed to have a programable safety control

system to avoid overdoses and an anti-theft system. I delivered my findings and

Keeping fit

I like jogging, boxing and biking. I ran in the AD Mini Marathon of 2014 and 2015 in Rotterdam.

Dutch Red Cross volunteer 2000 – 2004

I worked in large events such as concerts, football games and carnival parades as a first aid assistant.